A Guide to the Constituent Correspondence of Governor Lawrence Douglas Wilder, 1990.
Library of Virginia
- Series II. Governor's Office, 1990., Extent: 17.5 cubic feet (18 boxes). (Box 18-36)
  - Form letters - Abortion (90-23), 1990. (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Form letters - Weatherization (90-25), 1990. (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Form letters - Weatherization (90-25), 1990. (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Form letters - Weatherization (90-25), 1990. (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Form letters - Weatherization (90-25), 1990. (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Form letters - Weatherization (90-23), 1990. (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Form letters - Weatherization (90-25), 1990. (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Form letters - American Israel Public Affairs Committee - Con (90-26), 1990. (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Form letters - American Israel Public Affairs Committee - Con (90-26), 1990. (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Form letters - American Israel Public Affairs Committee - Pro (90-27), 1990. (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Form letters - Marine Resources Commission (90-30), 1990. (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Form letters - Non-Union employees (90-31), 1990. (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Form letters - Instructional setbacks (90-32), 1990. (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Form letters - Language academies (90-33), 1990. (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Form letters - Virginia Community Colleges cutbacks (90-34), 1990. (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Form letters - Western State Hospital (90-35), 1990. (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Form letters - Western State Hospital (90-35), 1990. (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Form letters - Western State Hospital (90-35), 1990. (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Form letters - Western State Hospital (90-35), 1990. (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Form letters - Western State Hospital (90-35), 1990. (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Form letters - Pornography - Heard on Geraldo Show (90-36), 1990. (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Form letters - Pornography - General (90-37), 1990. (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Form letters - Virginia Treatment Center for Children (90-38), 1990. (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Form letters - Virginia Treatment Center for Children (90-38), 1990. (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Form letters - Virginia Treatment Center for Children (90-38), 1990. (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Form letters - Virginia Treatment Center for Children (90-38), 1990. (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Fundraising Drive, 1990. (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - General, 1990. (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - General, 1990. (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - General, 1990. (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - General, 1990. (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - General, 1990. (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - General, 1990. (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Governor's appointments, 1990. (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Governor's correspondence - General, 1990. (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Governor's correspondence - General, 1990. (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Governor's correspondence - General, 1990. (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Governor's correspondence - General, 1990. (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Governor's correspondence - General, 1990. (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Governor's correspondence - General, 1990. (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Governor's correspondence - General, 1990. (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Governor's correspondence - General, 1990. (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Governor's correspondence - Ambassadors, 1990. (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Governor's correspondence - Attorney General, 1990. (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Governor's correspondence - Attorney General, 1990. (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Governor's correspondence - County officials and administrators, 1990. (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Governor's correspondence - Delegates, 1990. (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Governor's correspondence - Lieutenant Governor, 1990. (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Governor's correspondence - Mayors, 1990. (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Governor's correspondence - Other Governors, 1990. (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Governor's correspondence - Other Governors, 1990. (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Governor's correspondence - Personal friends, 1990. (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Governor's correspondence - President Bush, 1990. (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Governor's correspondence - Secretary of Economic Development, 1990. (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Governor's correspondence - Secretary of Finance, 1990. (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Governor's correspondence - Secretary of Transportation, 1990. (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Governor's correspondence - Senators, 1990. (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Governor's correspondence - Senators, 1990. (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Governor's correspondence - U.S. House, 1990. (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Governor's correspondence - U.S. House, 1990. (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Govenor's Fellows Program, 1990. (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Govenor's travel, 1990. (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Grayson Commission, 1990. (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Inaugural funds, 1990. (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Insurance claims, 1990. (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Japan External Trade Organization, 1990. (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Judges, 1990. (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Judicial Council, 1990. (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Judicial Inquiry and Review Commission, 1990. (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Kluge, 1990. (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Legislature, 1990. (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Legislature, 1990. (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Legislature, 1990. (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Letters from the Governor, 1990. (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - McFarlane, Walter, 1990. (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - McFarlane, Walter, 1990. (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Messages from the Governor, 1990. (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Messages from the Governor, 1990. (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Messages from the Governor, 1990. (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Messages from the Governor, 1990. (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Messages from the Governor, 1990. (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Messages from the Governor, 1990. (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Messages from the Governor, 1990. (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - National Commission of Inquiry, 1990. (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - National Governor's Association, 1990. (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - New River Valley, 1990. (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - News articles and clippings, 1990. (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - News articles and clippings, 1990. (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - No Authority - Federal, 1990. (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - No Authority - Federal, 1990. (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - No Authority - Judicial, 1990. (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - No Authority - Legal, 1990. (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - No Authority - Local, 1990. (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - No Authority - Local, 1990. (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - No Authority - Miscellaneous, 1990. (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Open House - July, 1990. (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Open House - August, 1990. (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Open House - August, 1990. (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Open House - September, 1990. (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Open House - October, 1990. (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Open House - November, 1990. (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Pastors and ministers, 1990. (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Pittston Coal Company, 1990. (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Policy, 1990. (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Presidential Scholars Program, 1990. (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Press Office - Davidson, Glenn, 1990. (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Press Office - Dillard, Laura, 1990. (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Press Office - Dillard, Laura, 1990. (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Press Office - Dillard, Laura, 1990. (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Press Office - Dillard, Laura, 1990. (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Press Office - Dillard, Laura, 1990. (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Press Office - Dillard, Laura, 1990. (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Press Office - Dillard, Laura, 1990. (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Press Office - Prosser, Michelle, 1990. (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Recommendations, 1990. (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Recommendations, 1990. (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Recommendations, 1990. (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Recommendations, 1990. (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Recommendations, 1990. (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Recommendations, 1990. (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Recommendations, 1990. (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Recommendations, 1990. (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Recommendations, 1990. (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Recommendations, 1990. (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Recommendations, 1990. (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Recommendations, 1990. (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Recommendations, 1990. (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Recommendations, 1990. (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Recommendations, 1990. (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Recommendations - Public Safety, 1990. (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Recommendations - Responses by Chief of Staff, 1990. (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Regrets from the Governor, 1990. (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Regrets from the Governor, 1990. (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Requests, 1990. (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Requests - Autograph or photograph, 1990. (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Requests - Autograph or photograph, 1990. (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Requests - Autograph or photograph, 1990. (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Requests - Autograph or photograph, 1990. (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Requests - Autograph or photograph, 1990. (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Requests - Autograph or photograph, 1990. (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Resignations, 1990. (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Resignations, 1990. (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Resignations, 1990. (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Resignations, 1990. (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Resignations, 1990. (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Resignations, 1990. (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Resolutions, 1990. (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Response from the Governor, 1990. (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Resumes, 1990. (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Resumes, 1990. (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Resumes, 1990. (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Resumes, 1990. (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Resumes, 1990. (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Resumes, 1990. (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Robb, Charles, 1990. (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Robb, Charles, 1990. (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - School Health, 1990. (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Schultze, Bob, 1990. (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Senate Clerk's Office, 1990. (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Senate and House Bills, 1990. (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Senate and House Bills, 1990. (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Senate and House Bills, 1990. (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Shropshire, Jay, 1990. (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Shropshire, Jay, 1990. (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Speeches, 1990. (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - State Corporation Commission, 1990. (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - State Corporation Commission, 1990. (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - State Corporation Commission, 1990. (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - State Corporation Commission, 1990. (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - State Lottery, 1990. (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - sympathy, 1990. (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Telegrams, 1990. (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Thank you letters from the Governor, 1990. (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Thank you letters from the Governor, 1990. (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Thank you letters from the Governor, 1990. (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Thank you letters from the Governor, 1990. (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Thank you letters from the Governor, 1990. (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Thank you letters from the Governor, 1990. (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Thank you letters from the Governor, 1990. (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Thank you letters from the Governor, 1990. (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Thank you letters from the Governor, 1990. (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Thank you letters from the Governor, 1990. (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Thank you letters from the Governor, 1990. (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Thank you letters from the Governor, 1990. (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Thank you letters from the Governor, 1990. (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Thank you letters from the Governor, 1990. (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Thank you letters from the Governor, 1990. (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Thank you letters from the Governor, 1990. (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Thank you letters from the Governor, 1990. (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Thank you letters from the Governor, 1990. (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Thank you letters from the Governor, 1990. (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Thank you letters from the Governor, 1990. (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Thank you letters from the Governor, 1990. (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Thank you letters from the Governor, 1990. (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Thank you letters from the Governor, 1990. (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Thank you letters from the Governor, 1990. (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Thank you letters from the Governor, 1990. (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Thank you letters from the Governor, 1990. (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Thank you letters from the Governor, 1990. (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Thank you letters from the Governor, 1990. (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Thank you letters to the Governor, 1990. (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Thank you letters to the Governor, 1990. (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Thank you letters to the Governor, 1990. (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Thank you letters to the Governor, 1990. (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Thank you letters to the Governor, 1990. (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Thank you letters to the Governor, 1990. (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Thank you letters to the Governor, 1990. (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Thank you letters to the Governor, 1990. (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Thank you letters to the Governor, 1990. (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Thank you letters to the Governor, 1990. (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Unanswered letters, 1990. (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Veterans of Foreign Wars, 1990. (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Virginia Credit Union, 1990. (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Virginia Liaison Office, 1990. (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Virginia State Bar, 1990. (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Virginia State Games, 1990. (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Workers' Compensation, 1990. (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Warner, John (U.S. Senator), 1990. (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Welcomes: Family Reunions, 1990. (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Word Access, 1990. (Box 36, Folder 6)
- Series III. Scheduling Office, 1990., Extent: 4.5 cubic feet (5 boxes). (Box 36-40)
  Scheduling Office correspondence, 1990, is housed in 5 boxes and is arranged chronologically. This series includes invitations to attend and requests for appearances by Governor Wilder at various events, as well as attached letter of regret. These Scheduling Office records arrived with this transfer of Constituent Correspondence. For additional Scheduling Office records see Records of the Scheduling Office of Governor Lawrence Douglas Wilder, 1989-1994 (Accession 35539, 34185).
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets, 1990 Jan. (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (1 of 4), 1990 Feb. (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (2 of 4), 1990 Feb. (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (3 of 4), 1990 Feb. (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (4 of 4), 1990 Feb. (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (1 of 6), 1990 Mar. (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (2 of 6), 1990 Mar. (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (3 of 6), 1990 Mar. (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (4 of 6), 1990 Mar. (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (5 of 6), 1990 Mar. (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (6 of 6), 1990 Mar. (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets - After General Assembly Session, 1990. (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (1 of 8), 1990 Apr. (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (2 of 8), 1990 Apr. (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (3 of 8), 1990 Apr. (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (4 of 8), 1990 Apr. (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (5 of 8), 1990 Apr. (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (6 of 8), 1990 Apr. (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (7 of 8), 1990 Apr. (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (8 of 8), 1990 Apr. (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (1 of 9), 1990 May. (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (2 of 9), 1990 May. (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (3 of 9), 1990 May. (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (4 of 9), 1990 May. (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (5 of 9), 1990 May. (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (6 of 9), 1990 May. (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (7 of 9), 1990 May. (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (8 of 9), 1990 May. (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (9 of 9), 1990 May. (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (1 of 9), 1990 June. (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (2 of 9), 1990 June. (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (3 of 9), 1990 June. (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (4 of 9), 1990 June. (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (5 of 9), 1990 June. (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (6 of 9), 1990 June. (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (7 of 9), 1990 June. (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (8 of 9), 1990 June. (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (9 of 9), 1990 June. (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (1 of 5), 1990 July. (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (2 of 5), 1990 July. (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (3 of 5), 1990 July. (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (4 of 5), 1990 July. (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (5 of 5), 1990 July. (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (1 of 5), 1990 Aug. (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (2 of 5), 1990 Aug. (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (3 of 5), 1990 Aug. (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (4 of 5), 1990 Aug. (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (5 of 5), 1990 Aug. (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (1 of 8), 1990 Sept. (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (2 of 8), 1990 Sept. (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (3 of 8), 1990 Sept. (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (4 of 8), 1990 Sept. (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (5 of 8), 1990 Sept. (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (6 of 8), 1990 Sept. (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (7 of 8), 1990 Sept. (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (8 of 8), 1990 Sept. (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (1 of 9), 1990 Oct. (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (2 of 9), 1990 Oct. (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (3 of 9), 1990 Oct. (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (4 of 9), 1990 Oct. (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (5 of 9), 1990 Oct. (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (6 of 9), 1990 Oct. (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (7 of 9), 1990 Oct. (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (8 of 9), 1990 Oct. (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (9 of 9), 1990 Oct. (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (1 of 9), 1990 Nov. (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (2 of 9), 1990 Nov. (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (3 of 9), 1990 Nov. (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (4 of 9), 1990 Nov. (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (5 of 9), 1990 Nov. (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (6 of 9), 1990 Nov. (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (7 of 9), 1990 Nov. (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (8 of 9), 1990 Nov. (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (9 of 9), 1990 Nov. (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (1 of 2), 1990 Dec. (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets (2 of 2), 1990 Dec. (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets - Holds, 1990. (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets - Holds, 1990. (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets - Miscellaneous (Individual), 1990. (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets - Miscellaneous, 1990. (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets - Miscellaneous, 1990. (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets - Miscellaneous, 1990. (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets - Miscellaneous, 1990. (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets - Miscellaneous, 1990. (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets - Miscellaneous, 1990. (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets - Miscellaneous, 1990. (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets - Miscellaneous, 1990. (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Scheduling Requests and Regrets - Southern Governor's Conference, 1990. (Box 40, Folder 20)